curtisandhayes.com 2015-11-27

# Privacy Policy Curtis & Hayes

### 1\. Curtis & hayes APPROACH TO PRIVACY

1.1   www.curtisandhayes.com is a website operated by Curtis & Hayes (India) Private Limited (we, our, us). We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy sets out how we collect, use and share information that identifies you or is associated with you (“personal information”).

1.2   For the purposes of the Personal Data. (Protection) Act, 2013, we are the data controller of the personal information we hold about you.

1.3   You should also be aware that we use cookies to store and access information whilst providing access to our site. You can find out more about our use of cookies in our Cookie Policy.

### 2\. PERSONAL INFORMATION WE HOLD ABOUT YOU

2.1   We collect personal information from you when you voluntarily submit information directly to us or our website. This can include information you provide when you register to use the site, create an account on our site and interact with other users, complete a form, enter competitions through our site, correspond with us, purchase products from the site, subscribe to our email lists or respond to surveys or promotions.

2.2   We also collect personal information indirectly from you such as information about the pages you look at on the site or the device you connect to the site with. We may also collect personal information about you from third parties such as other users of the site.

2.3   We describe the categories of personal information we collect in more detail below:

(a) Contact details: such as your name, your email address, your telephone number and addresses associated with your account.

(b) Profile information: such as your contact details (as above) and other any information you share when creating a profile on our website.

(c) Comments and opinions: such as comments and opinions you share on our website or when you respond to our surveys, competitions and promotions.

(d) Messages to us or between users: messages you send to us such as email and written correspondence and messages to other users using review on the product page.

(e) Payment and transaction information: we will keep records of the products and services you purchase from us and the payment method you use for the transaction.

(f) Login profile information: third-party service (e.g., Facebook) login details and profile information such as your log-in token, user name and photo and other information from that service as permitted by you and that service.

(g) Your preferences: choices you make such as notification and messaging preferences or choices about how the site is displayed.

(h) Information about how you use and connect to the online service

(i) We collect information about how you use the site such as the pages and links you access, the time you access the site and duration you are on it, the website you come to the site from or go to after leaving the site and selections and choices you make when using the site.

(ii) We also collect information about the computer or other electronic devices you use to connect to the site such as details about the type of device (which can include unique device identifying numbers), its operating system, browser and applications connected to the site through the device, your Internet service provider or mobile network, your IP address and your device’s telephone number (if it has one).

(iii) Typically, the information we collect about how you use or connect to the site is associated with your device and not you as a named individual. However, if you are logged into a registered account this information may also be associated with you directly.

(i) Information about your location: Other than information you choose to provide to us, we do not collect information about your precise location. Your device’s IP address may help us determine an approximate location but this will be no more precise than the city, state or country you are using your device in.

(j) Information about the location of purchases: We will display a catalogue image of any purchase through our site on a searchable map as a way of showing the approximate location of the delivery address you give when making a purchase. We do not disclose any personally identifiable information on our map and only display our catalogue image of the purchase you made by reference to the pin code of the delivery address.

(k) Information provided by other users: Sometimes, other visitors to our site provide information that is associated with you. For example, other visitors may provide information that is associated with you when they invite you to use the website.

(l) Information provided by other organisations: Other organisations may provide information that we associate with you where they are lawfully permitted to share it, such as contact details, demographic data, or Internet navigation information.

(m) Information from fraud and crime prevention organisations: If fraudulent or other criminal activity is suspected relating to your account, we may be provided with information by credit reference, fraud and crime prevention organisations.

### 3\. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

3.1   We will also use your personal information for the purposes specifically described below:

(a) Contact details: we will use your contact details so that we can communicate with you directly about the products we sell and the service we provide and about queries, issues or concerns you or other users have. We may also use your contact details to send you information about products and services that may be of interest to you (such communications will be in accordance with your marketing preferences).

(b) Profile information: we use your profile information to provide our service to you and ensure that you are able to interact with our users as permitted by the functionality of the service and your preferences.

(c) Comments and opinions: We will use your comments and opinions to determine products and services that may be of interest to you and to provide our service to you and ensure that you are able to interact with our users as permitted by the functionality of the service and your preferences.

(d) Payment and transaction information: we will use payment and transaction information you provide to process payment for any product or service you purchase from us. We may also use the history of your transactions with us to determine products and services that may be of interest to you.

(e) Messages to us or other users: we will use messages you send to us to help us respond to any query, issue or concern you raise and to provide our service to you and ensure that you are able to interact with our users as permitted by the functionality of the service and your preferences.

(f) Your preferences: we will use your preference settings for the purpose of providing notifications, messages, displaying the site and following other choices you are able to make about how the site is displayed to you.

(g) Information about how you use and connect to the online service: we use this information to present the site to you on your device. We will also use this information to determine topics, products and services that may be of interest to you.

(h) Information about your location: we may use an approximate location to ensure content on the site is relevant to the city, state or country you are using your device in. We will not collect or track your exact location without your consent.

(i) Information about the location of purchases: we use this information to show what types of purchases are being made in a particular area on a searchable map and to allow users to contact other users about their purchasers either directly through reviews or through us depending on your preferences.

(j) Information provided by other users: We will use your personal information that is contained in messages sent to us by other users to respond to any query, issue or concern they raise or to provide our service to you and ensure that you are able to interact with our users as permitted by the functionality of the service and your preferences. We will use your personal information that is contained in forms submitted by other users to contact you, if they indicate you would like to receive a communication from us.

(k) Information about fraudulent or criminal activity relating to your account: we will use information about fraudulent or criminal activity relating to your account for the purposes of preventing fraud or crime.

(l) All personal information: will use all the personal information we collect to: (i) monitor and improve the site and our procedures and processes; and (ii) to help us develop new products and services. Our use of your personal information in this way will not result in information that was not previously publicly available being made public on the site. We will also not use information about fraudulent or criminal activity relating to your account in the development of new products and services.

3.2 We may anonymise and aggregate any of the information we collect (so that it does not directly identify you). We may use anonymised information for purposes that include testing our IT systems, research, data analysis, improving the site, developing new products and features or displaying information about the purchases made via our site such as the most popular purchases or purchases based on an approximate location.

### 4\. INFORMATION WE SHARE WITH THIRD PARTIES

4.1   We may share your personal information with the following parties:

(a) Our users: we and you may share your information with other users as part of our service so you are able to interact with our users as permitted by the functionality of the service and your preferences.

(b) Companies in the same group of companies as us: our subsidiaries (i.e. any organisation we own or control) or our ultimate holding company (i.e. any organisation that owns or controls us) and any subsidiaries it owns. These companies will only use your personal information in the same way as we can under this privacy policy.

(c) Service providers and advisors: third parties who provide a service to us, for example, we use a third party delivery service to deliver any products you buy to your address. These third parties will only be allowed to use your personal information in accordance with our instructions and will be required to keep your information secure.

(d) Purchasers of our business: personal information may be disclosed or transferred to buyers or prospective buyers of our business or any of our assets as part of the sale.

(e) Law enforcement, regulators and other parties for legal reasons: third parties who we are under a legal obligation to disclose your personal information to or who we need to disclose your personal information to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of others, detect and investigate illegal activities and breaches of any agreement we have with you.

4.2 We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to anyone else except as set out above. We may provide third parties with aggregate statistical information and analytics about users of the site but we will make sure no one can be identified from this information before we disclose it.

### 5\. MARKETING AND ADVERTISING

5.1  Email Marketing - From time to time we may contact you by email with information about our products and services. If you do not want us to send you email marketing, please let us know by sending an email to us at contact@curtisandhayes.com. You can also unsubscribe from our marketing emails by clicking on the unsubscribe link (where available) in the emails we send to you.

5.2  Email Notifications About On Behalf of Users – We may send you notifications that users may wish to contact you about purchases you have made through our site. If you wish to speak to the user, you may do so on review page. If you do not want us to send these notifications, please let us know by sending an email to us at contact@curtisandhayes.com.

5.3   Email Notifications About Your Order or Changes to the Services We Provide - We may send you email notifications when in relation to your order or changes to the way we provide our services to you.

5.4   Advertising on the Site and other Websites – We, or our advertising partners, may show advertisements to you on our site or on other websites. To do this we, or our advertising partners, may collect information about how you use the site or the types of other web pages, content and ads you, or others who are using the device you connect to the site, interact with, visit or view. The information collected might also include the IP address of the device you connect to the site. We, or our advertising partners, use the information that is collected to make sure adverts you see either on the site or other websites or apps (where our partners have advertising space) are more relevant to you.  
The techniques our advertising partners use recognise the device you are using but are not aimed at you as a named individual. Typically cookies and similar technologies are used to provide this type of advertising. You can find out more about cookies and how to manage their use by reading our Cookies Policy.

### 6\. STORING AND TRANSFERRING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

6.1   Cookies and Local Storage: we may store information (which may include personal information) locally on your device using cookies and other browser and application storage methods. For further information please see our Cookies Policy.

6.2   International Transfers of your Personal Information: the personal information we collect may be transferred to and stored in countries outside of the jurisdiction you are in. Some of these jurisdictions offer differing levels of protection in respect of personal information and may, in certain instances, be less protective than the jurisdiction you are typically resident in. We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

### 7\. ACCESSING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

7.1   If there is information you would like to access, please contact us using the contact details set out in the “Contact us” section below. Please provide as much information as you can about the information you are looking for and we will be happy to try and help you find it.

### 8\. LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES

8.1   The site may, from time to time, contain links to and from third party websites of our partner networks, advertisers, partner merchants, news publications, retailers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies. Please check the individual policies before you submit any information to those websites.

### 9\. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

9.1   We may update this privacy policy from time to time and so you should review this policy periodically. When we change this privacy policy in a material way, we will update the “last modified” date at the bottom of this privacy policy. Changes to this privacy policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

### 10\. NOTICE TO YOU

10.1   If we need to provide you with information about something, whether for legal, marketing or other business related purposes, we will select what we believe is the best way to get in contact with you. We will usually do this through email or by placing a notice on the site. The fact that we may send notices to you will not stop you from being able to opt out of certain types of contact as described in this privacy policy.

### 11\. CONTACTING US

11.1   Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcome and should be addressed to contact@curtisandhayes.com .
